RYAN ROSALES

User Experience Designer and Prototyper

Creative and highly-motivated User Experience Designer with a strong foundation in Graphic Design and Typography. I specialize in experience design and prototyping to provide time-efficient and cost-effective design processes for businesses. Currently focused on learning and building AR/VR experiences.

Portfolio: https://ryanrosales.com/ Email: ryancrosalesl@gmail.com

Linkedin: ryancrosales **Phone**: (559) 283-5997

Experience

Lennar Corporation | User Interface Designer

February, 2021 - April, 2021

Responsible for designing web pages for various residential communities in the San Francisco, Bay Area.

Infinite Peripherals | Design Intern

October, 2019 - January, 2020

Designed the UI and 20-foot marketing display for NRF in collaboration with the design, engineering, and marketing teams. Responsible for the UI design and direction of product landing pages in collaboration with Otterbox and Oracle. Worked in Sketch to design assets and manage design systems.

Freelance | UX/UI Designer

May, 2019 - August, 2020

Worked with product management to research, design and deliver a mobile app for a automotive company. Designed and delivered a personal website for a Senior Full-Stack Developer. Worked with a startup in Irvine, California to redesign their landing page and spearheaded the design of a web app MVP.

Education

Introduction to XR: VR, AR, and MR Foundations

Coursera. Issued Jan. 2021.

No Expiration Date.

California State University, Fullerton

August, 2017 - May, 2020

Graphic and Interactive Design Specialization

Relevant Coursework: Intro to Psychology, Web and Interactive Design, Typography A, B and C.

Skills

Design	Research	Languages	Tech
AR/VR	Interviews	HTML/CSS	Figma
Web/Mobile	Surveys	C#	Adobe CC
Typography	Journey mapping		Principle
Wireframing	Usability testing		Unity 3D
Prototyping			Blender
3D			A-Frame
30			Vuforia
			ARFoundation

Selected Projects

Healthcare Training (Virtual Reality)

May, 2021 - June, 2021

Managed and spearheaded the end-to-end design process. Executed 3D modeling in Blender and user interfaces and programming in Unity.

Tested prototypes at varying fidelities to validate concepts. Conducted primary and secondary research, and 1-on-1 interviews.

Career Counseling (Mobile App)

May, 2021

Concerted secondary and primary research, survey, and competitive analysis to validate the weight of the problem. Performed userflows, user interface design, prototyping and testing.

Crunchyroll (Website Redesign)

August, 2020

Commanded primary research and surveys to identify user pain points. Conducted secondary and market research to align solutions to current business values. Executed user interface design and prototyping.